Uh Uh Too Spicy
You want my A to the Z
But you won't get it, not a chance
But you won't Tidak mungkin
But you won't 無理に決まってる
But you won’t 어림없지
But you won't 想的美
But you won't Còn lâu mới được
Take your pick, Sweet or Freak?
Coba tebak Sweet atau Freak
当ててみて Sweet または Freak
맞혀봐 Sweet 또는 Freak
猜猜看 Sweet 或 Freak
Đoán thử xem Sweet hay là Freak
What’s hiding underneath (I see)
Sittin' on the fence, Oh, ain't got a chance
Kau yang mencicipi seperti ragu-ragu, tak ada kesempatan Oh
躊躇うように探りを入れる君 チャンスはない Oh
망설이듯 간 보는 너 기회는 없어 Oh
犹豫着试探的你没有机会 Oh
猶豫不決 試水溫的你沒有機會 Oh
Cứ dò xét lưỡng lự như anh thì chẳng có cơ hội đâu Oh
Nah You won’t get it
No No, You won’t get it
I say
Pulled in in a blink of an eye, You'll be mine (Mine)
Dalam sekejap aku menarikmu You'll be mine (Mine)
ぱっと一瞬で引き寄せる You'll be mine (Mine)
깜빡 한순간 끌어당겨 You’ll be mine (Mine)
在眨眼一瞬间将你拉近 You'll be mine (Mine)
一個瞬間將你拉近 You’ll be mine (Mine)
Lôi cuốn anh trong tức khắc You'll be mine (Mine)
Get closer Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Mendekatiku diam-diam Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
そっと近づいてきて Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
살짝 다가와 Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
微微靠近 Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
靠過來一些 Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Rồi lại gần một chút Can cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Every day got you bored
Every day membuatmu bosan
君を退屈にさせていた Every day
널 따분하게 했던 Every day
让你无聊至极的 Every day
讓你枯燥乏味的 Every day
Mỗi ngày từng khiến anh buồn chán Every day
Gonna throw down some fun traps
Aku akan memberimu jebakan yang menarik
面白い罠を投げてあげるわ
흥미로운 덫을 던져줄게
为你布下饶有趣味的陷阱
為你設下有趣的陷阱
Vậy để tôi bày ra một cái bẫy thú vị
Jump on in
Coba lompatilah
飛び込んでみて
뛰어들어 봐
跳进来吧
等你上勾
Nhảy vào đi nào
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
You tiptoe into my heart
Menyusup ke hatiku, kau
心に入り込む 君は
심장을 파고들어 넌
你钻入我心脏
你鑽入我心臟
Anh đi sâu vào trong trái tim tôi
I'm too Spicy
While the fire spreads
Dalam perasaan yang menyebar, kau
滲む刺激の中で君は
번지는 자극 속에 넌
你在不断蔓延的刺激里
你在不斷蔓延的刺激裡
Trong cơn rạo rực dần lan tỏa
In that very moment
Pada saat itu
ちょうどその瞬間
바로 그 순간
就在那一瞬间
就在那個瞬間
Vào đúng khoảnh khắc đó
Finding another part of me
Menemukan aku yang lain
また違う私を発見する
또 다른 나를 발견해
发现另一个我
發現另一個我
Tôi nhận ra một bản thể khác của mình
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop, don't be scared
Don't Stop Jangan takut
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
Don’t Stop 겁내지 마
Don't Stop 不要怕
Don't Stop 別害怕
Don't Stop Đừng sợ hãi
Bang Bang, shout it out
Bang Bang Teriakan
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
Bang Bang 大喊吧
Bang Bang 大聲喊
Bang Bang Cứ hét lên đi
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop, be brave now
Don’t Stop Beranilah
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Don’t Stop 용기 내 봐
Don't Stop 鼓起勇气
Don't Stop 鼓起勇氣
Don't Stop Mạnh mẽ lên nào
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy
Too Spicy too too
Tell me what you see
When you look at me
'Cause I am a 10 out of 10 honestly
A different energy, this Move
Move dengan kekuatan berbeda
勢いが違う Move
기세가 다른 Move
气势不同的 Move
氣勢凌人的 Move
Bước chân với khí thế khác thường Move
Overpowering Groove
Groove yang menguasaimu
君を圧倒する Groove
널 압도하는 Groove
将你压倒的 Groove
壓制你的 Groove
Cùng giai điệu trấn áp anh Groove
But you keep wasting your time Dude
Don't chase me, I'm warning you
Don't chase me aku memperingatkanmu
Don't chase me 警告する 私は
Don't chase me 경고해 난
Don't chase me 我发出警告
Don't chase me 我發出警告
Don't chase me Tôi cảnh cáo đấy
Erase me, run far away
Erase me Larilah sejauh mungkin
Erase me 遠くに逃げて
Erase me 멀리 달아나
Erase me 远远逃离
Erase me 遠遠逃離
Erase me Bỏ chạy cho xa đi
Hey, you get it now?
Hey Apa kau mengerti sekarang
Hey もう分かる？
Hey 이젠 알겠니
Hey 现在知道了吗
Hey 現在懂了嗎
Hey Giờ anh đã biết chưa
I was born Bad I'm so bad honestly
Dari awal Bad I’m so bad honestly
元々 Bad I’m so bad honestly
원래부터 Bad I’m so bad honestly
原本我就很 Bad I'm so bad honestly
我本來就 Bad I'm so bad honestly
Tôi vốn đã Bad I'm so bad honestly
So bad
Want it all, gonna Call you mine now (Mine)
Aku ingin semuanya mulai sekarang Call you mine (Mine)
全部私のものにする これからは Call you mine (Mine)
전부 가질래 지금부턴 Call you mine (Mine)
我要拥有一切 从现在起 Call you mine (Mine)
我要擁有全部 從現在起 Call you mine (Mine)
Muốn sở hữu tất cả, vậy từ giờ Call you mine (Mine)
If you gonna dip, Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Jika kau akan melarikan diri Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
逃げるなら Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
도망칠 거면 Don’t cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
如果想逃走 Don't cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
要逃跑的話 Don't cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Có muốn chạy trốn thì Don't cross my borderline (Line Line Line)
Every day the same old, same old
Every day yang selalu jelas
いつもありきたりだった Every day
늘 뻔하기만 했던 Every day
总是那么老套的 Every day
總是太老套的 Every day
Mỗi ngày vẫn luôn chán chường Every day
Time now to toss that Rule
Sudah waktunya untuk lepas dari Rule
もう Ruleから外れるとき
이제 그만 Rule을 벗어날 때
现在是时候从 Rule 中摆脱出来
是時候從 Rule 當中脫身了
Giờ đã đến lúc ta thoát khỏi những luật lệ Rule
Ain't hard to do
Itu tak sulit
難しくない
어렵지 않아
没什么难度
一點都不難
Chẳng có gì khó đâu
Just right now
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
You tiptoe into my heart
Menyusup ke hatiku, kau
心に入り込む 君は
심장을 파고들어 넌
你钻入我心脏
你鑽入我心臟
Anh đi sâu vào trong trái tim tôi
I'm too Spicy
While the fire spreads
Dalam perasaan yang menyebar, kau
滲む刺激の中で君は
번지는 자극 속에 넌
你在不断蔓延的刺激里
你在不斷蔓延的刺激裡
Trong cơn rạo rực dần lan tỏa
In that very moment
Pada saat itu
ちょうどその瞬間
바로 그 순간
就在那一瞬间
就在那個瞬間
Vào đúng khoảnh khắc đó
Discovering yet another me
Menemukan aku yang lain
また違う私を発見する
또 다른 나를 발견해
发现另一个我
發現另一個我
Tôi nhận ra một bản thể khác của mình
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Ready? Uh
Gimme the next level, Next Next Next
Naikkan intensitasnya sedikit, Next Next Next
もう少し強度を上げて 次、次、次
좀 더 강도를 높여 다음다음다음
再加大强度 继续继续继续
再提高一點強度 再來再來再來
Mạnh mẽ lên nữa đi, tiếp tục đi
One of a kind
Beyond our limits, Wow Wow Wow
Kita berada di depan batas Wow Wow Wow
私たちは限界の先を行く Wow Wow Wow
우린 한계를 앞서 Wow Wow Wow
我们超越极限 Wow Wow Wow
我們超越極限 Wow Wow Wow
Ta vượt lên giới hạn của chính mình Wow Wow Wow
That’s Right
'Cause I’m too Spicy for your heart
Ring the fire alarm
Completed another challenge
Setelah tantangan baru, kau
新しい挑戦の末に君は
새로운 도전 끝에 넌
在全新挑战的尽头 你
在全新挑戰的最後 你
Sau khi anh đương đầu với thử thách mới
I'm too Spicy
It's your time to change
Sudah waktunya untuk berubah, kau
変化する時間だよ 君は
변화할 시간이야 넌
是时候该改变了 你
是時候改變了 你
Đã đến lúc anh phải thay đổi
Right this moment
Pada saat ini
今この瞬間
지금 이 순간
就在这一瞬间
這個瞬間
Ngay tại khoảnh khắc này
Finding another part of me
Menemukan aku yang lain
また違う私を見つけ出す
또 다른 나를 찾아내
找到另一个我
找到另一個我
Tôi lại tìm ra một bản thể khác của mình
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
Don't Stop, don't be scared
Don't Stop Jangan takut
Don't Stop 怖がらないで
Don’t Stop 겁내지 마
Don't Stop 不要怕
Don't Stop 別害怕
Don't Stop Đừng sợ hãi
Bang Bang, shout it out
Bang Bang Teriakan
Bang Bang 叫んでみて
Bang Bang 외쳐봐
Bang Bang 大喊吧
Bang Bang 大聲喊
Bang Bang Cứ hét lên đi
I’m too Spicy Yeah I’m too Spicy
You know that I
Don't Stop, be brave now
Don’t Stop Beranilah
Don't Stop 勇気を出してみて
Don’t Stop 용기 내 봐
Don't Stop 鼓起勇气
Don't Stop 鼓起勇氣
Don't Stop Mạnh mẽ lên nào
Next step, Myself
I’m too Spicy I’m too Spicy
I’m too Spicy too too I’m too Spicy
'Cause I
Oh Yeah
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
(Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart)
Finally comes the feeling of Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Akhirnya menyebarkan Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
ついに滲んでくる Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
마침내 번져오는 Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
终于蔓延而来的 Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
終於蔓延而來的 Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Và cuối cùng là niềm vui lan tỏa Joy (Enjoy joy joy joy)
Yeah I’m too Spicy for your heart
I’m too Spicy too too
I’m too Spicy
For you